Hello friends, I am Vishal and
welcome everyone to my two wheeler village. So
Aamir Hui 4G has met with an accident and is in
such a bad condition that the
entire portion of the handle is crushed in a church in Europe. So
friends, how do you repair it?
But I am going to tell you all about the vehicle in
detail through my film. So
friends, before this I have picked up an Activa
vehicle, but that Activa had a
little normal damage, the entire band baja fixed on the left side,
I repaired it and made it good. It was a low budget.
I will try to make this also good. So
friends, this Activa has a very bad
accident portion.
What will be there in it, what will be
needed, but how will I repair it, so
you will come to know that this
vehicle has become like this after stopping for ₹10, so
you stay in my video
so that you can get complete information about
how I repair this vehicle and
change it on Friday so that the
engine can run well.  If you are
not doing the video, let's brush it. If you are visiting my channel for the
first time, then please do like and
subscribe. Let's
start the video. We are going to
tell you in this video that do it.
[Music]
Do it.
Then it is wrong. The car of these nursing men has been
damaged. It is safe and sound. If the
car is damaged, it will be repaired. So let's do it for the
good of the country. Let us arrest the commissioner
and tell him
that do it.
You have fallen asleep. We have kept the entire car in front. We have
sworn to remove it
from the car.
[Music] The
first wish has been fulfilled.
What is the condition of the car now? Let me show you
that we will complete it as soon as possible. We will do its
friend.
A horrible body app. The left place will be repaired from power point.
1000 teams will put it so that all the meter
fame will try to can it, pending it, and then
cutting it again. So
let's start working on the car right now.
[Music]
222 and we have done a total of 5 videos, so let's do the
fitting. Plus I will make you new
sandals.
and then after that sparing hips and these are
our fanning
that I am calling oh pouring our dinner Gauri
this is the body and this is the side panel declared
so let's start we have to do the
fitting
in me Tripti and minister are present
222 we have commented on the car the
handle will fold it inwards do this do it that it has happened that it has happened that the
first one which was done the car is completely complete
see this now
[music]
Ajay to
Ajay
that when we start it and
show it as soon as possible
[music]
Ajay to
Ajay